[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "How did you find it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "find", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "He just crushed it, Matthew.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "just", "crushed", "it", ",", "Matthew", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "ORGAN: Did you enjoy it?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "enjoy", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "I did, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Have you ever met one who isn't?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "met", "one", "who", "is", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Well, now when you say powerful, what do you mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "now", "when", "you", "say", "powerful", ",", "what", "do", "you", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well as in somebody who's not necessarily in the entertainment game, he's not famous as a celebrity but has real power.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "as", "in", "somebody", "who", "'s", "not", "necessarily", "in", "the", "entertainment", "game", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "famous", "as", "a", "celebrity", "but", "has", "real", "power", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "And they say they don't want any of it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "say", "they", "do", "n't", "want", "any", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, they go like and hang on about how awful fame is and they moan away about it all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "go", "like", "and", "hang", "on", "about", "how", "awful", "fame", "is", "and", "they", "moan", "away", "about", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "But, I've seen you beyond this a few times saying, you know what -- everybody wants to be famous, right?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "I", "'ve", "seen", "you", "beyond", "this", "a", "few", "times", "saying", ",", "you", "know", "what", "--", "everybody", "wants", "to", "be", "famous", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "ACON: Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["ACON", ":", "Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "It's exactly how I would be feeling, if I had made 50 films of the quality you have and I still haven't had my moment, seeing some of the clowns that walk away with those gardens (ph) -- I mean, it's going to get to you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "exactly", "how", "I", "would", "be", "feeling", ",", "if", "I", "had", "made", "50", "films", "of", "the", "quality", "you", "have", "and", "I", "still", "have", "n't", "had", "my", "moment", ",", "seeing", "some", "of", "the", "clowns", "that", "walk", "away", "with", "those", "gardens", "(", "ph", ")", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "get", "to", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", ":", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Here's the thing -- I mean, I don't act for statues.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "thing", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "act", "for", "statues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Was that a joke?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "a", "joke", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I was kidding.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "kidding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "How did you get caught -- how did you get caught up in the whole Madoff thing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "caught", "--", "how", "did", "you", "get", "caught", "up", "in", "the", "whole", "Madoff", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You know, it was recommended that we -- we put, you know, some money with him and we did.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "was", "recommended", "that", "we", "--", "we", "put", ",", "you", "know", ",", "some", "money", "with", "him", "and", "we", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Have you said how much?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "said", "how", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "I mean, at the absolute peak of your time with Madoff, how much did you think you had?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "at", "the", "absolute", "peak", "of", "your", "time", "with", "Madoff", ",", "how", "much", "did", "you", "think", "you", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "ACON: I'd rather not say.", "answer_tokens": ["ACON", ":", "I", "'d", "rather", "not", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Madoff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Without giving the amount, what was the percentage of -- of your wealth that was committed to this?", "question_tokens": ["Without", "giving", "the", "amount", ",", "what", "was", "the", "percentage", "of", "--", "of", "your", "wealth", "that", "was", "committed", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Wow, that's a good question.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "I mean, this is horrendous, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "this", "is", "horrendous", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "It wasn't good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "n't", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "What was the moment you knew that this was all going belly up?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "you", "knew", "that", "this", "was", "all", "going", "belly", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Got a call, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Got", "a", "call", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Did you get any money back at all?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "any", "money", "back", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "In terms of a life realignment -- what did it do to you and your wife and as a family do you think, in terms of how you now look at life?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "a", "life", "realignment", "--", "what", "did", "it", "do", "to", "you", "and", "your", "wife", "and", "as", "a", "family", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "how", "you", "now", "look", "at", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, I think that it's a good way to think about what you have to be grateful for.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "good", "way", "to", "think", "about", "what", "you", "have", "to", "be", "grateful", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "I mean, you -- you've done well, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "--", "you", "'ve", "done", "well", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Yes, she's a knockout.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "she", "'s", "a", "knockout", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Clay"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Clay Bertrand?", "question_tokens": ["Clay", "Bertrand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Yes, Clay.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Clay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Sexual purposes?", "question_tokens": ["Sexual", "purposes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Did he pay you for this?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "pay", "you", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Twenty dollars each time.", "answer_tokens": ["Twenty", "dollars", "each", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What was Hollywood like when you go through the dry out process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "Hollywood", "like", "when", "you", "go", "through", "the", "dry", "out", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, it's tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Martin Short"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 231, "question": "When you've tasted some real glory?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'ve", "tasted", "some", "real", "glory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, you know, there's -- there's a great line in a -- that Martin Short has in a movie that we're doing -- he plays my agent and things aren't -- I'm a -- I'm a director in the movie and things aren't going well and his -- his character says, \"Well, frankly everyone wants to distance themselves from the stench.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "--", "there", "'s", "a", "great", "line", "in", "a", "--", "that", "Martin", "Short", "has", "in", "a", "movie", "that", "we", "'re", "doing", "--", "he", "plays", "my", "agent", "and", "things", "are", "n't", "--", "I", "'m", "a", "--", "I", "'m", "a", "director", "in", "the", "movie", "and", "things", "are", "n't", "going", "well", "and", "his", "--", "his", "character", "says", ",", "``", "Well", ",", "frankly", "everyone", "wants", "to", "distance", "themselves", "from", "the", "stench", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Only six?", "question_tokens": ["Only", "six", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Yes, it's six degrees.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "six", "degrees", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "How about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Fascinating.", "answer_tokens": ["Fascinating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "That idea?", "question_tokens": ["That", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Well, the charitable way that you've done this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "charitable", "way", "that", "you", "'ve", "done", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Do you see evidence that it works?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "evidence", "that", "it", "works", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "When you make people think like that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "make", "people", "think", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Well, I mean, I think that we have a long way to go in terms of our specific site.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "that", "we", "have", "a", "long", "way", "to", "go", "in", "terms", "of", "our", "specific", "site", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Pretty cool, right?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "cool", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "How did you meet?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "meet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, the truth is, is that I was doing a play down in the Village in -- a real long time ago, and I had a matinee and an evening performance and during -- after the matinee, I went to the deli and I was buying a sandwich.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "truth", "is", ",", "is", "that", "I", "was", "doing", "a", "play", "down", "in", "the", "Village", "in", "--", "a", "real", "long", "time", "ago", ",", "and", "I", "had", "a", "matinee", "and", "an", "evening", "performance", "and", "during", "--", "after", "the", "matinee", ",", "I", "went", "to", "the", "deli", "and", "I", "was", "buying", "a", "sandwich", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 321, "question": "ORGAN: What -- and how did you then get together?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "--", "and", "how", "did", "you", "then", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", ":", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, then, years later --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "then", ",", "years", "later", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Years later?", "question_tokens": ["Years", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "But has she said she harbored some weird thought about you since that deli moment?", "question_tokens": ["But", "has", "she", "said", "she", "harbored", "some", "weird", "thought", "about", "you", "since", "that", "deli", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Did you know she was the one?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "she", "was", "the", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What is -- what is the reason why so many show business marriages flounder, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "--", "what", "is", "the", "reason", "why", "so", "many", "show", "business", "marriages", "flounder", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Well, I'd never actually seen the statistics that there's any more divorce in show business than there is in any other thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'d", "never", "actually", "seen", "the", "statistics", "that", "there", "'s", "any", "more", "divorce", "in", "show", "business", "than", "there", "is", "in", "any", "other", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "How have you managed to resist the lure of the groupie, for lack of a better phrase?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "managed", "to", "resist", "the", "lure", "of", "the", "groupie", ",", "for", "lack", "of", "a", "better", "phrase", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, I mean, I don't -- I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "How would you feel if your kids wanted to get into the business?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "feel", "if", "your", "kids", "wanted", "to", "get", "into", "the", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, you know, it's weird.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "weird", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "I've heard you don't ever watch your films.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "heard", "you", "do", "n't", "ever", "watch", "your", "films", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "You never rewatch an old movie?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "rewatch", "an", "old", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Just there's so much that I feel like I wish I'd done differently that it's kind of like torture.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "there", "'s", "so", "much", "that", "I", "feel", "like", "I", "wish", "I", "'d", "done", "differently", "that", "it", "'s", "kind", "of", "like", "torture", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "You're such a perfectionist that you just see so many things you wish you'd done in a different way?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "such", "a", "perfectionist", "that", "you", "just", "see", "so", "many", "things", "you", "wish", "you", "'d", "done", "in", "a", "different", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "And it's just too much agony, you can't watch it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "'s", "just", "too", "much", "agony", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "watch", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "What is the one Kevin Bacon movie, if I forced you to watch again at gunpoint, you would watch?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "one", "Kevin", "Bacon", "movie", ",", "if", "I", "forced", "you", "to", "watch", "again", "at", "gunpoint", ",", "you", "would", "watch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Oh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kevin Bacon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Is that the dream role for you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "dream", "role", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Well, you don't -- you're not happy you're middle-aged until, I guess, you're middle-aged because what other choice do you have?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "--", "you", "'re", "not", "happy", "you", "'re", "middle-aged", "until", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "you", "'re", "middle-aged", "because", "what", "other", "choice", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "That's a terrible gift.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "terrible", "gift", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Have any of you three discussed colonoscopies with your friends over a few beers?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "any", "of", "you", "three", "discussed", "colonoscopies", "with", "your", "friends", "over", "a", "few", "beers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Letterman"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Well, I got that idea because I saw on the -- either Letterman or whatever.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "got", "that", "idea", "because", "I", "saw", "on", "the", "--", "either", "Letterman", "or", "whatever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "Are you sort of resistant to be tagged with them here?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sort", "of", "resistant", "to", "be", "tagged", "with", "them", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Well, you know, I mean, in my mind I'm not above, you know, five and twenty.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "in", "my", "mind", "I", "'m", "not", "above", ",", "you", "know", ",", "five", "and", "twenty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What's the worst thing about getting middle-aged?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "worst", "thing", "about", "getting", "middle-aged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "It's not bad at all.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "bad", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Well, I think we really appreciate it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "really", "appreciate", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Or do you see some negatives in the aging process?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "see", "some", "negatives", "in", "the", "aging", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Well, I don't -- I keep -- my biggest problem is I think that I'm still -- I'm not middle-aged and that I'm 20 years younger.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "keep", "--", "my", "biggest", "problem", "is", "I", "think", "that", "I", "'m", "still", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "middle-aged", "and", "that", "I", "'m", "20", "years", "younger", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "You don't age as much in the mirror, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "age", "as", "much", "in", "the", "mirror", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Well, you mentally feel it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "mentally", "feel", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "JJR", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "How am I old?", "question_tokens": ["How", "am", "I", "old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Andre talked about you learn about life more, so when you get to middle age, you can almost appreciate the reality of life.", "answer_tokens": ["Andre", "talked", "about", "you", "learn", "about", "life", "more", ",", "so", "when", "you", "get", "to", "middle", "age", ",", "you", "can", "almost", "appreciate", "the", "reality", "of", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Is that something -- do you learn enough that you start to appreciate what life really is?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "something", "--", "do", "you", "learn", "enough", "that", "you", "start", "to", "appreciate", "what", "life", "really", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Well, you get perspective.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "get", "perspective", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "What's been the biggest mistake you've ever made?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "biggest", "mistake", "you", "'ve", "ever", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Whoa.", "answer_tokens": ["Whoa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Ray?", "question_tokens": ["Ray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I hope it's a good one because we could use a story idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "it", "'s", "a", "good", "one", "because", "we", "could", "use", "a", "story", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "PRP$", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Or do you have genuine look back and think, yeah, that was a deciding moment?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "have", "genuine", "look", "back", "and", "think", ",", "yeah", ",", "that", "was", "a", "deciding", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I regret things hour to hour, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "regret", "things", "hour", "to", "hour", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What are you talking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "The one with all the women.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "one", "with", "all", "the", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "When you were falling about laughing there watching your own show, which is always encouraging.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "falling", "about", "laughing", "there", "watching", "your", "own", "show", ",", "which", "is", "always", "encouraging", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "You quite like this new stage of your life, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "quite", "like", "this", "new", "stage", "of", "your", "life", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "If you could give advice to a 16-year-old Ray Romano, what would you tell him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "give", "advice", "to", "a", "16-year-old", "Ray", "Romano", ",", "what", "would", "you", "tell", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Oh lord.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "lord", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ray Romano"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "A 16-year-old Ray Romano?", "question_tokens": ["A", "16-year-old", "Ray", "Romano", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ray Romano"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "What kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Oh, I had in my 20s, I didn't know what I wanted to do, and my brother had just gotten married, and he moved out of the house.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "had", "in", "my", "20s", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "what", "I", "wanted", "to", "do", ",", "and", "my", "brother", "had", "just", "gotten", "married", ",", "and", "he", "moved", "out", "of", "the", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Had one in the 30s too?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "one", "in", "the", "30s", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Yeah, I had like a very anxiety-ridden, and I had a little emotional struggle there for like a year or two in my 20s.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "had", "like", "a", "very", "anxiety-ridden", ",", "and", "I", "had", "a", "little", "emotional", "struggle", "there", "for", "like", "a", "year", "or", "two", "in", "my", "20s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Scott, what would you say, if you were talking to a young Scott, what would you tell him?", "question_tokens": ["Scott", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", ",", "if", "you", "were", "talking", "to", "a", "young", "Scott", ",", "what", "would", "you", "tell", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Oh, a young Scott.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "a", "young", "Scott", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Scott"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "You must have had some wild days?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "had", "some", "wild", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "I'm being quiet now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "being", "quiet", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 673, "question": "How important is it to find the right woman?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "it", "to", "find", "the", "right", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 674, "answer": "It's essential, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "essential", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Do you Twitter?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "Twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "No, I do not Twitter.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "not", "Twitter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sophia Loren"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Who would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I would say from the past, or not even -- Sophia Loren.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "from", "the", "past", ",", "or", "not", "even", "--", "Sophia", "Loren", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn Monroe"]}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "Any of you going to go for the classic middle aged crisis?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "of", "you", "going", "to", "go", "for", "the", "classic", "middle", "aged", "crisis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "I'll go for Marilyn Monroe.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "go", "for", "Marilyn", "Monroe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Can I take Marilyn?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "take", "Marilyn", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "None of you are going for the classic stereotypical middle aged crisis woman.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "of", "you", "are", "going", "for", "the", "classic", "stereotypical", "middle", "aged", "crisis", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 722, "question": "Why did he get Sophia Loren?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "he", "get", "Sophia", "Loren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 723, "answer": "She is still alive.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "is", "still", "alive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sophia Loren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "It was movie that never came out.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "movie", "that", "never", "came", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110610pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "But I watch it every night.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "watch", "it", "every", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]